(Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org)
[This program is intended for
audiences aged 13 and over]
[It may contain
explicit visuals, audio, and content;
viewers under the age of 13
should be advised]
After three years, our love
seems to be going beautifully,
but still, there are
some days when we fight.
Here you go.
If I have to wait
just for you to be 30 minutes late,
I won't give you rides anymore.
I have to rush to my class, too.
If you were in a hurry,
why didn't you call me?
I could've come down
without showering.
Jane,
I called you three times,
but you never picked up.
[Missed calls from Dai]
I... I'm sorry.
I didn't bring my phone
into the bathroom,
so I didn't hear your calls.
Next time, I'll come here myself.
I'm not gonna bother you anymore.
I'm also thinking
that I won't give you rides anymore.
Because it's time we move in together.
Huh?
What did you say?
Here.
We're pretty worn out already.
Should we pick this up tomorrow?
No way.
I don't want to make a mess
from the first day.
Then how about
you take a shower to freshen up?
I'll put your clothes away
in our closet.
Nuh-uh, no.
Are you sure?
Where are you going?
I'm so sweaty.
Don't you think I smell bad?
It's not like
it's the first time you're sweaty.
Ju!
What's up?
It's just...
I need to pick your brain on something.
What's going on?
You know that...
I'm moving in with Dai today, right?
I...
I'm just wondering...
Like...if my butt itches,
do I scratch it in secret?
Trust me,
it's gonna be like that at first,
but after some time, you're gonna
scratch your butt right in front of her.
That can't be!
It's not just for you, though.
She's gonna do it, too.
You guys are gonna be more comfortable
and open with each other.
Then, you're saying that if it itches,
I can just go for it?
Bet.
Eek!
Aren't you gonna peel it first, Jane?
I thought it was an apple.
Can you sleep?
Jane?
Are you already asleep?
Not yet.
It's probably the first-night effect
keeping me from falling asleep.
Does it give you peace of mind
with me by your side?
Yes.
Dai?
Yes?
From now on,
please take care of me.
You, too.
My university life
is flying by so fast.
With only a blink of an eye,
I'm already a junior.
And this girl
is my first-year peer mentee,
named 'Kim.'
Here you go.
Whoa, Jane.
You bought me desserts again.
Do you want me to have a chubby face?
The desserts from this place
are really good, Kim.
You do remember
that my family owns a bakery, right?
Anyway, thank you,
JaneWill!
Kim!
I told you not to call me
by that name, didn't I?
Just 'Jane,' not 'JaneWill'!
Why not?
I think 'JaneWill'
has a nice ring to it.
It's totally unique.
Plus, everyone on campus knows it.
Kim!
How about this?
I'll also change my name to 'KimWill.'
That way, everyone will know
we're a mentor and a mentee.
JaneWill and KimWill.
Watch it!
Well, then, I'm going to class.
Thanks again,
JaneWill!
Jane, come eat your favorite
stir-fried rice noodles with soy sauce.
Just a sec. Let me reply to my texts.
What's going on?
Normally, if she knew I bought her
this favorite dish of hers,
she would leave everything
and jump right at it.
Today, though, she seems different.
Who's she texting?
Jane,
another minute and it's gonna get cold.
Jane!
I'm done!
Whoa!
It smells incredible.
Come on,
the first bite is yours.
Here.
Here comes the choo-choo train!
Is it good?
Leave them there; I got it.
No,
I got it.
Go take a seat, Dai.
Didn't your mom say...
you always break dishes?
Who got you smiling like that?
I'm not even doing anything.
You're imagining it.
So you're just smiling to yourself?
That's odd.
Was there a phenomenon last night?
Hm?
Phenomenon?
What phenomenon?
The Two Moons!
Rewind, Kaning.
Nothing you said makes sense.
- The Two-Moon phenomenon?
- Mm!
What's that supposed to mean?
Tell me.
You're totally out of the loop.
Jane and Dai
have already moved in together!
Wait, deadass?!
Totally!
Could've led with that!
So, was it as sweet as a honeymoon?
Rong, what nonsense!
You're so dirty-minded!
What? When girlfriends are together...
If you don't help me
with the group project today,
I'll be crossing your name out!
Ooh!
Miss Darin, my dearest of friends...
Miss Darin, the beauty,
I was merely teasing you.
From now on,
I'll refrain from doing so.
But don't you think
our bestie here looks sleep-deprived?
I guess the Moon rose all night long!
Stop it!
What even was that?
You're crazy.
You gotta keep up
with the nourishment now.
Want some coffee?
- I'm jelly!
- Me too.
I had so much fun and so much food.
It was so spicy, though.
Was it?
- Have you eaten?
- I have.
You don't do spicy, right?
Such a baby.
So, how are you guys doing in classes?
Jane, I'm here.
Give me five.
Sure.
That...
is Dai.
Stay here. I have to go.
Bye-bye!
Bye.
Let's go.
What should we have for dinner?
Who was that girl?
Oh, Kim!
The first-year peer mentee
I always told you about.
Right...
She's pretty cute.
True!
Kim is such a nice and adorable girl!
She's not picking up
what I'm putting down
about me not wanting to see her
getting close to that kid?
Let's go now.
Come on, are you hungry?
Let's get going!
What should we have for dinner?
How about noodles at Rong's shop?
She's sound asleep.
Are you mad...
Who'd get mad at your cute little face?
Jane, what do you wanna have for dinner?
I'll go ahead and order it for you.
You can just order what you need.
I'm gonna be home a little late.
Where are you going?
Just running some errands.
Who are you going with?
A friend?
Uh, with...
With a freshman.
A freshman?
Is that Kim, her peer mentee?
Then, when are you gonna be done?
I'll come get you home.
How so?
I have your motorbike with me.
I have my way.
Just send me the location.
Dai, don't you have to meet
the deadline?
You don't have to come.
I'm hanging up.
Jane!
Who's that freshman?
Where did you guys go?
How many people were there?
Just the two of you?
Wow, that feels like an investigation.
Which one
do you want me to answer first?
Just answer me.
I went there with Kim.
There were two of us.
Where did you go?
It's a secret.
I'll tell you all about it later.
I'm taking a shower, Dai.
I'm going now.
I'll tell you later.
I'm off.
Hey, look.
- Hm?
- Look.
- That's frying me!
- Right?
What's going on, Miss Darin?
You look pretty tense.
Is that Botox or something?
Cut the jokes.
I'm not in the mood for those today.
I saw you two
being so in love just the other day.
Or is it that...
she broke up with you?!
Jeez, I'm sure it's not that serious.
Don't just say things.
Jane's been acting differently.
Different how?
She's way too close
with that peer mentee.
They went out one-on-one
without even telling me.
Last night was even more infuriating.
She came home at almost 9 P.M.!
I knew it! I can smell the sus.
Well, freshmen, right?
They have bright little faces,
unlike some ancient seniors.
If you don't want to end up heartbroken,
you gotta keep an eye on them.
Rong, don't be so foul-mouthed.
There's probably nothing going on.
But I mean it.
Well, what about what we talked about?
Did your family say yes?
Of course, no sweat.
That's nice!
But you gotta promise me
that you'll keep this a secret.
Well, wouldn't Dai be mad at me
if she found out?
Then,
we have to make sure she doesn't!
Dai's coming.
Dai, how did you get here?
Walking.
Then, how long have you been here?
Long enough to see you
sit here with your peer mentee.
You're Kim, aren't you?
Yes.
Did you eat something spicy earlier?
You're so feisty.
Then, excuse me.
Gorgeous,
you have such beautiful eyes.
Ow, ouch,
my eyes are burning
from your unmatched beauty again!
We need to talk.
Uh...
There's really nothing going on, Dai.
Even though she's your peer mentee,
you don't have to be this close.
I'm sorry, Dai.
I'll try not to be chummy
with Kim like that again.
Jane!
I'm... I'm coming home.
It's gonna be just a sec.
Don't hang up just yet!
Where are you now?
It's a secret.
I'm hanging up now.
Jane?
Why did Dai sound so stern?
Has she...
caught me?
Probably not, right?
Where did you guys go?
How many people were there?
I went there with Kim.
There were two of us.
I'm coming in!
Jane,
this isn't funny.
I've set up the room
and prepared this place,
along with some fried chicken,
since this evening,
and this is when you decided
to come home?
You don't value today at all.
Dai, you're being so harsh.
Well, look at what you did.
Have you ever even cared about me?
Uh, I...
Go on.
I'm waiting for your explanation.
Jane...
Jane?
Kim's family owns a bakery,
so I applied for a baking course
to surprise you with a cake.
That means...the reason you're close
with your peer mentee lately
is that you wanted
to bake a cake to surprise me?
All this time,
you've been taking
such good care of me,
so I thought...
I wanted to do
something special for you.
Jane...
I'm so sorry
that I...
Dai...
were you jealous?
Uh...
I...
I was just...a little jealous.
Heh-heh.
Here.
I love what you've done with the place.
I also wanted to surprise you.
I'm sorry
for causing the misunderstanding.
It's all good.
I'm not gonna plan
a surprise for you anymore.
Hey!
Absolutely not.
You gotta do it again sometimes.
But...
Just don't keep it a secret from me.
What? If I don't keep it a secret,
how is it supposed to be a surprise?
Good question.
I really misunderstood Kim.
I don't know
if she already hates me at this point.
I don't think so.
And you don't have to worry about Kim
because she's already taken.
Besides...
I...
love being alone.
Huh?
"Love being alone"?
♫I love being alone,♫ as in...
I love being alone with you.
What am I gonna do to you? Hm?
Why?
Well, you're giving me cute aggression.
♫I love being alone♫
Come on, I'll feed you.
How about this? Is it too big?
Is it?
Fine, go on.
- Big bite.
♫Just a gaze from you
warms my heart away♫
♫Just your smile from you
paints the whole world anew♫
♫Nothing's ever the same♫
♫Don't know when it all began,♫
♫Suddenly, I can't get you off my mind♫
♫Guess you are the sweetest kind♫
♫Every time you are near,
I feel at ease♫
♫There's a warmth in me
that has increased♫
♫You're the one coloring my sky♫
♫Every time you are near,
I feel at ease♫
♫You're too cute,
no way I can deny that♫
♫You're my comfort zone,
don't let go of me♫
[Directed by SUEASIAM STUDIO]
I don't think that works.
- Try again.
- Let's try again.
So cute!
Cut.
I'm sorry.
Cut...
Was that too fast?
I'm sorry.
Greetings to both of you.
Why the bow?
What's with the gesture?
- Huh? What did you say?
- What...
- Pearmai...
- What was that, sweetie?
Girls, once you've had
enough snicks and dranks...
"Snicks and dranks."
It's, "Snacks and drinks."
- Wait, wait.
- Hold on, girls.
Goodbye.
Hold on, let's try that again.
- We're not done.
- I'm sorry.
- Not yet.
- Auntie, just stay cool for now.
I'm sorry. I'll order them
to cancel all the flights.
"Are you working for an airline?"
Ugh...Jane...
I almost won the jackpot back.
Always happens to me!
Action.
I heard through the grapevine...
- Let me make the face.
- Someone's revving their engine.
Cut.
Jane will take care of the dishes.
Wait...
It's, "I'll."
Come on, do that again.
I'll take care of the dishes.
Go right in.
Can you help Jelly face this way?
Jane, is that you?
Mom, you have to act like
you think she already picks up.
- Oh.
- Right, I have to...
Here, I'll put it on a plate.
I'm not hungry anymore!
Why didn't you snatch it?
- Why didn't you?
- You gotta snatch it.
- Ooh, that's right.
- Snatch it.
- Give it to me, Junior.
- Heck no.
- Give it to me!
- Give it to me.
- Heck no.
Junior!
I'm moving back in with...
I'm going back to the condo.
One more time.
I'm not worried...
Oops!
- "I'm not worried..."
- One more time.
How about you tell them yourself?
They're all here,
except Mom...
How about you tell them yourself?
Only Dad is missing.
Try again, he misspoke.
- Lock me up. Mom's standing...
- Sorry.
Just in time,
you come...
- "You came just in time."
- Right.
Just in time...
Jeez, why am I like this?
It's time for food.
Hi, Mom.
You got your line wrong again.
- "You came just in time for food."
Cake doesn't like anyone
at first,
but in reality, she's nice.
You missed your line there.
"Cake? That's just how she is."
We never seem to change.
There's a motorbike passing by.
- Let's do that one more time.
- Let's do it.
I done asked...
I'm sorry.
How is it?
Still as good as ever?
- That doesn't work. Move over a bit.
- Move a bit.
I know you're trying
to steal my thunder.
- Cut.
- You're overthinking it.
Wow, did you really have
to work this hard, Darin?
Come on, reset.
- Go back to where you were.
- Walk back.
We just wanna know.
Why'd she get mad at us for?
I'm sorry.
- Continue.
- Go back.
Not yet.
- Just a sec.
- Go back out.
Let's go.
Have a safe trip back.
You missed the mark.
- You gotta be on it.
- Okay.
It wasn't a kiss!
It was just a peck!
Vroom.